(Penny:)No. No, not really.
(Penny:)Listen, didn't you say
you needed some eggs?
(Sheldon:)Yes, but anyone who knows anything
about bacterial growth...
(Sheldon:)...knows to pick up their refrigerated foods
on the way out.
Oh, okay, maybe you should start
heading on out, then.
(Sheldon:)No, this is fun.
(Sheldon:)The thing about tomatoes,
and I think you'll enjoy this...
(Sheldon:)...is they're shelved with the vegetables,
but they're technically a fruit.
- Hmm. Interesting.
- Isn't it?
(Penny:)No, I mean what you find enjoyable.
(Sheldon(as Penny selects vitamin supplements):)Oh, boy.
(Penny:)What now?
(Sheldon:)Well, there's some value
to taking a multivitamin...
(Sheldon:)...but the human body
can only absorb so much.
(Sheldon:)What you're buying here
are the ingredients for very expensive urine.
(Penny:)Well, maybe that's what I was going for.
(Sheldon:)Well, then you'll want some manganese.